

Deimantas Miklušis

Front-End Web Developer Al Specialist





+370 6 2737252



deiwulf@gmail.com



Lithuania, Kaunas

₩ Skills

- Full-Stack Web Development
- Extensive Technical Expertise
- Project Management & Resource Coordination
- SEO & Digital Marketing
- Al & Automation Proficiency
- Media Editing & Enhancement
- Game Testing & Modding
- Research & Data Management
- Virtual Assistance & Moderation
- Attention to Detail & Quality Assurance
- Analytical & Critical Thinking
- Independence & Resourcefulness
- Depression:)

🛂 Languages

- English (all) Fluent
- Lithuanian Native

About Me

Quality result-oriented, highly adaptive, somewhat eccentric, and introverted technology enthusiast who gets things done.

I'm thoroughly familiar with every layer of web development, however, my highest expertise and passion are within Front-End and, recently, AI application and development.

Currently active freelance and open to remote opportunities where I can exercise and grow those Front-End development and/or AI skills.



Education

Bachelor of Science, Informatics 2010 - 2014 | Kaunas University of Technology



Experience

- Front-End Web Developer | IT | AI Specialist 2015 - Present | Freelance
 - Building and face-lifting websites
 - SPA's (Single Page Applications) using React or Vue
 - Converting designs (PSD, PNG, etc.) to HTML to CMS
 - · Applying screen responsiveness (with and without Bootstrap)
 - Implementing custom effects/interactivity via JavaScript/CSS
 - · Various fixes and optimizations, utilizing best practices
 - SEO, PPC (Google Ads)
 - Tech support
 - Training and integrating various AI models and tools

Overall tech stack:

HTML5, CSS3|Sass, Bootstrap, JavaScript(ES6+|Babel|jQuery| REST|React|Vue), CMS(WordPress, TYPO3), nodeJS, PHP (not active), MySQL/NoSQL(mongoDB), Git, Webpack|Gulp, AHK, Python and various AI tools like ComfyUI, Forge webUI, RooCode, etc.

Web Developer | IT Support 2013 - 2015 | Volunteering - Various Programming experience of HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, MySQL and CMS (TYPO3).

Diagnostics, maintenance, hardware/software repair and/or installation, computer building, remote IT support.